

IULIA CRISTINA POP

UX/UI DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

As a UX/UI designer, my primary focus is to gain a deep understanding of user needs to finally implement the best designed solution. Since 2020, I've enjoyed working in SME, agencies and corporations. I have a wealth of experience in crafting intuitive, user-friendly, and visually appealing digital experiences across various platforms and devices. My passion lies in creating products that not only meet user needs but also exceed their expectations, resulting in increased user satisfaction and engagement.

CONTACT

(+40) 770581227, Bucharest, Romania

E-mail: iuliapop.ux@gmail.com LinkedIn: <u>Iulia Cristina Pop</u>

Portfolio: Iulia Pop

EDUCATION

MOBILE USER EXPERIENCE, WEB ACCESSIBILITY, UI DESIGN PATTERNS, USER RESEARCH

2022-2023 | Certificate Courses by Interaction Design Foundation

DESIGN LED STRATEGY: Design thinking for business strategy and entrepreneurship

2022 | Certificate Course by University of Sydney

PRODUCT DESIGN

2022 | Course by GOOGLE- Udacity

CAREER FOUNDRY (Berlin, Germany)

2019-2020 Certificate Course in UX Design & Front-end Development Specialization

UNIVERSITY OF MEDICINE AND PHARMACY "CAROL DAVILA"

2016-2018 Master's degree in Physical Therapy (UNEFS) 2012-2015 Bachelor's degree in Physical Therapy

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021-NOW | SUSTAINALYTICS- MORNINGSTAR (UX Designer) INTERNAL PROJECTS: ADA, COVERAGE CHECK

- Conduct qualitative user interviews to understand customer needs, create engaging and user-friendly design concepts, and identify pain points in user journeys.
- · Apply creativity and logic to build products from scratch and demonstrate exceptional stakeholder management skills.
- Develop design strategies aligned with company goals, collaborating with cross-functional teams, and presenting concepts to clients and stakeholders.

TOOLS: AdobeXD, Figma, FigJam, Asana, Jira, ServiceNow

2022-2023 | DELOITTE DIGITAL TECHNOLOGIES (UX/UI Designer) PROJECT: CUSTOMS CLEAR

- Create high-quality UX deliverables, such as wireframes, interactive prototypes, personas, and user journey maps for successful project outcomes.
- · Synthesize insights from user and stakeholder research to shape design work.
- Lead workshops and collaboration sessions, review systems for UX issues, and provide actionable recommendations. Stay updated on UX and tech trends, fostering inclusive teamwork within Deloitte Digital's design methodologies.

TOOLS: Figma, Miro, Jira, Confluence

2021 RADICAL 13 Creative Studio (UX/UI Designer) PROJECT: Technologywithin

- Redesign the website pages for existing products for both web and mobile platforms.
- Improve the onboarding experience and optimize the UI layout through the creation of wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and low-fidelity clickable prototypes to guide product development.
- Emphasize UX expertise in crafting visual styles for new product features.

TOOLS: Figma, FigJam, Slack

SOFT SKILLS DESIGN SKILLS DESIGN TOOLS Communication Balsamia User Research Visual Presentation Figma Accessibility Planning management Adobe XD Information Architecture Miro Wireframming Detail oriented Problem solving **InVision** Prototyping **Usability Testing** 0000 Team work Critical thinking